The Screwiest Comedy of the Year!
3 Nuts in Search of a Bolt is a comedy film directed by Tommy Noonan.
An out-of-work method actor is hired by a male model, an ecdysiast,
and a car salesman who live together to save money.
They want the actor to listen to their problems and go see a
psychiatrist, so they can get counseling for cheap.
The psychiatrist is intrigued by the split personalities indicated by the three separate sets of problems presented by the actor, and soon producers
are climbing out of the woodwork trying to buy the rights to the film, while the actor is having trouble keeping his act together.
Saxie Symbol, played by Mamie Van Doren.
Tom, played by Tommy Noonan.
Dr. Myra Von, played by Ziva Rodann.
Bruce Bernard, played by John Cronin.
Dr. Otis Salverson, played by Howard Koch.
Henry, played by T.C. Jones.
3 Nuts in Search of a Bolt is a 1964 comedy film starring Mamie Van Doren
and Tommy Noonan, who also directed and co-wrote the film.
The film explores themes of money, model, psychiatrist, unemployed.
The tone is lighthearted.